All right, Phoebe?
피비!
좋아, 내가 어느날 갑자기
전지전능해진다면
If I were omnipotent for a day,
I would want world peace...
세계 평화와 기아 방지를
위해 힘쓰고
...no hunger, good things
for the rain forest.
열대 우림을 보호할 거야
가슴도 키울거야
And bigger boobs.
Well, see, you took mine.
내 대신 다 해버렸네
What about you?
챈들러, 넌 어때?
If I were omnipotent for a day,
I'd make myself omnipotent forever.
내가 갑자기 전능해진다면
영원히 전능하게 만들어야지
꼭 이런 사람들이 있다니까
There's always one guy. "lf I had a
wish, I'd wish for three more wishes. "
'소원을 하나 이뤄준다고?
세 가지 소원을 이뤄주세요'
Hey, Joey.
- 안녕?
- 어서 와, 조이
안녕, 친구
What would you do
if you were omnipotent?
조이, 네가 전능해진다면
어떻게 할 거야?
죽어버려야지
Probably kill myself.
Excuse me?
뭐라구?
꼬맹이 조이가 힘을 못 쓰면
살아갈 이유가 없잖아
If little Joey's dead,
then I got no reason to live.
조이, 전능하다면 말야
Joey, omnipotent.
You are?
너 불능이야?
Ross, l' m sorry. I had no idea. I
thought it was a theoretical question.
몰랐어
그냥 좀 우울한 줄만 알았지
The One With the George Stephanopoulos
How does she do that?
어떻게 저럴 수 있지?
난 사람들 많은 데서
못 자는데
I can't sleep in a public place.
Libraries, airplanes,
movie theaters....
도서관, 비행기, 극장...
오빠 어릴 땐
그랜드캐년에서 잤어
You slept at the Grand Canyon.
뭐? 엄마 아빠가 그런 데
데려가신 적이 없어
Hello, Mom and Dad never took us
to the Grand Canyon.
Mom and Dad took us
to the Grand Canyon?
엄마 아빠가 날
그랜드캐년엘 데려갔었어?
표정 좀 봐
얼마나 평화로워 보여?
Would you look at her?
She is so peaceful.
그러게...
Yeah.
What? What? What?
왜, 무슨 일이야?
안녕
-Hi.
-It's okay. You just nodded off again.
괜찮아
자다가 놀란 것 뿐이야
왜 그래?
What's going on?
- 어제 통 잠을 못 잤어
- 왜?
I got no sleep last night. My
grandmother has a new boyfriend...
할머니한테 새 남자친구가
생겼는데
침대가 불안하시다는 거야
...and they' re both kind of insecure
in bed, so And deaf.
돌아가시겠대
서로 좋아하는 거 누가
모를까봐 계속 티를 내시는데
They reassure each other
that they' re having a good time.
얼마나 요란했는지 말도 못해
You have no idea how loud they are.
- 괜찮으면 우리집에서 자
- 고마워
-You can stay with Rachel and me.
-Thanks.
95, 96, 97
95, 96, 97. See, I told you.
내가 뭐랬어, 우리집에서
100걸음도 안된다니까
Less than 1 00 steps
from our place to here.
너도 참 할 일 되게 없다
You got way too much free time, man.
생일 맞은 친구 아냐?
There's the birthday boy.
로스, 이것 봐
Hockey tickets. Rangers-Penguins
tonight and we're taking you.
레인저스랑 펭귄스 팀 하키
시합 있는데 우리가 데려가 줄게
- 생일 축하해, 친구
- 사랑한다, 친구
-Happy birthday, pal!
-We love you, man.
It's funny. My birthday
was seven months ago.
별일이네
내 생일은 7달 전이었잖아
그래서?
-So?
-So you had an extra ticket...
티켓이 하나 남았는데
같이 갈 사람이 없어서 그렇지?
...and couldn't decide
who got to bring a date?
넌 너무 부정적인
경향이 있어
Well, aren't we
Mr. The-Glass-ls-Half-Empty?
맙소사,
Oh, my God! Is today the 20th?
October 20th?
오늘이 10월 20일이야
기억 못했으면 했는데
-I hoped you wouldn't remember.
-What's wrong with the 20th?
20일이 어쨌는데?
할로윈 11일 전인데 의상이
하나도 안 남았어?
Eleven days before Halloween.
All the good costumes are gone?
오늘은 캐롤하고 내가 육체적인
관계의 절정을 느낀 날이야
T oday's the day Carol and I first...
...consummated our...
... physical relationship.
섹스 말야
Sex.
모니카한테 얘기했어?
-You told your sister that?
-Believe me, I told everyone.
우린 전부 다 얘기해
난 하키 구경 관둘래
I better pass on the game.
집에 가서 헤어진 부인이랑
레즈비언 애인 생각이나 해야지
I'm just gonna go home and think about
my ex-wife and her lesbian lover.
하키는 무슨 하키
우리도 그러자
The hell with hockey!
Let's all do that!
무슨 소리야, 로스
얼음 왕자 셋이 뭉쳐야지
Come on, Ross! You, me, Joey, ice!
Guys' night out!
어떻게 할 거야, 어?
Come on, what do you say, big guy?
- 뭐하는 거야?
- 나도 몰라
-What are you doing?
-I have no idea.
가자, 로스
-Come on, Ross.
-Maybe it will take my mind off it.
좋아, 시합 구경하다보면
잊혀지겠지
- 나 '왕손가락' 사주는 거다?
- 그래!
-Promise to buy me a big foam finger?
-You got it.
이것 봐
나 첫 월급 받았어
Look, look, look! My first paycheck!
내 이름이 써있어
안녕, 레이첼?
Look at the window!
There's my name! Hi, me!
I remember when
I got my first paycheck.
나도 첫 월급 타던 날이
생각난다
광산에 사고가 나서
여덟 명이 죽었지
There was a cave-in in a mine,
and eight people were killed.
너 광산에서 일했어?
-You worked in a mine?
-No, I worked at a Dairy Queen. Why?
아니, 아이스크림 가게
왜?
정말 굉장하지 않니?
내 손으로 번 거야
Isn't this exciting? I earned this.
I wiped tables for it. I steamed milk.
테이블 닦고 우유 데우고
그렇게 일해서...
And it was totally...
푼돈 벌었네
... not worth it.
보험분담금이 뭔데
내 돈을 다 가져가는 거야?
What's FlCA?
Why's he getting all my money?
챈들러, 이것 좀 봐
I mean, what?
Chandler, look at that.
이 정도면 괜찮은 거야
This is not that bad.
그럼, 첫 월급치고는
You're fine, yeah, for a first job.
이 정도면 먹고 살기
충분하지
You can totally,
totally live on this.
그럼 그럼
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
그건 그렇고
수고가 많은데 팁이라도 주자
-By the way, great service today.
-Yeah.
- 하키!
-Hockey!
하키!
-Hockey.
레이첼?
Rachel?
세상에!
Oh, my God!
동물의 왕국에서 새들이
저러는 거 봤어
I swear I've seen birds
do this on Wild Kingdom.
여긴 웬일이야?
What are you doing here?
쇼핑하다 너희 엄마 만났는데
네가 여기 있다잖아
We were in the city shopping, and your
mom said you work here, and it's true!
근데 정말이네
앞치마 두른 거 보니까
연극하는 것 같다
Look at you in the apron.
You look like you're in a play.
세상에, 너 정말 배가 많이
불렀구나
God, look at you! You're so big!
I can't believe it!
알아, 알아
내가 좀 많이 나왔지?
I know, I know! I'm a duplex.
키키, 많이 변했다
살이 왜 이렇게 빠졌어
IKiki, you look phenomenal. I mean,
you've lost, like, a ton of weight.
And you should...
정말 정말 멋지다
좋아 보여
... really, really It's time to stop,
you look perfect.
그래, 넌 요즘 어때?
What's going on?
아빠가 공동 경영자로
누굴 뽑았게?
Well, guess who my dad's
making partner in his firm?
소식 얘기가 나왔으니
말인데...
And while we're on
the subject of news....
이것 봐, 나 팔꿈치 있다
Look, look! I have elbows!
Passes it up to Leetch.
로스, 리치에게 패스
리치, 니스 선수를 봅니다
패스!
Leetch spots Messier. Here's the pass!
메시 선수, 여자 신발을 보느라
정신없어 타임아웃 합니다
We'll take a time-out while Messier
looks at some women's shoes.
캐롤은 부츠를 신었지
그 날은 우리가 처음...
Carol was wearing boots just like
those the night that we first....
있지...
You know? In fact, she....
캐롤은 절대 부츠를
벗지 않았어
She never took them off.
왜냐하면 우린...
미안해
It's because we Sorry, sorry.
왜?
I can't believe
- 복숭아씨야
- 왜, 갉아먹게?
-What?
-Peach pit.
Yes, bunny?
복숭아씨, 그날 밤 우린...
복숭아를 먹었어
Peach pit. That night, we had
-Peaches?
-Actually, nectarines but....
사실 깡통에 든 거였지만...
그것도 복숭아지
Could've been a peach.
그 뒤에 옷을 입고
버스 정류장에 데려다줬지
Then we Then we got dressed
and I walked her to...
...the bus stop. I' m fine.
괜찮아
저 여자 엉덩이 캐롤이랑
똑같다
Hey, that woman's got
an ass like Carol's.
왜, 똑같은 거 찾기
게임하는 거 아니었어?
What? I thought we were
trying to find stuff.
재밌는 얘기 좀 해봐
Come on, you guys.
T ell me all the dirt.
뭐니뭐니해도 네가 배리를
버린 게 최대 사건이지
Well, the biggest news is still you
dumping Barry at the altar.
-Let's talk reality for a second.
-Okay.
- 우리 현실적인 얘길 해보자
- 좋아
- 집에 언제 올 거야?
- 뭐?
-When are you coming home?
-What? Guys, l' m not.
안 가
괜찮아, 우리잖아
-Come on. This is us.
-l' m not.
안 가, 난 지금이 좋아
일도 있고
This is what l' m doing now.
I've got this job.
내 손으로 빨래도 해
I even do my own laundry.
이건 내 직업이야
-This is what l' m doing now.
-Waitressing?
웨이트리스가?
그것만 하는 게 아냐
I' m not just waitressing.
I mean, l' m....
오늘의 특별 요리 란에
특별 요리도 적어 넣고
I write the specials
on the specials board.
꽃병에서 죽은 꽃도 꺼내놓고
And I take the dead flowers
out of the vase.
Sometimes Arturo lets me put the
chocolate blobbies on the cookies.
가끔은 쿠키에 초코 눈도
박아 넣고...
Well, your mom didn't tell us
about the blobbies.
네 엄마가 초코 눈 말씀은
안 하셨는데...
레이첼, 친구들하고는 어땠어?
Hey, Rach.
How was it with your friends?
모니카 만의 특별 펀치를
드시겠습니까?
Okay, how would you like
some Tiki Death punch?
뭐가 들었는데?
-What's that?
-Well, it's rum and
- 럼주하고...
- 줘
Okay.
피비가 우리집에서 자기로
했으니까 우리 파자마파티 하자
Since Phoebe's staying,
we'll have a slumber party.
야한 잡지도 있고 쿠키도 있고
트위스터도 있어
We got trashy magazines.
We got cookie dough. We got Twister.
'군사작전'도 가져왔어
And I brought Operation. But I lost
the tweezers so we can't operate.
핀셋을 잃어버려서
작전 짜기는 좀 힘들지만
대원들 훈련시키면 돼
But we can prep the guy.
레이첼, 카드 회사야
-Rach, it's the Visa card people.
-Oh, God. Ask them what they want.
무슨 일인지 좀 물어봐줘
무슨 용무신지 저한테
말씀 하실래요?
Could you please tell me
what this is in reference to?
잠깐만요
There's been unusual
activity on your account.
네 신용카드 사용 실적이
이상이 있어 전화했대
요즘 카드를 통 안 썼는데
I haven't used my card in weeks.
그러니까 이상한 거지
That is the unusual activity.
너 괜찮냐고 물어보는데
They wanna see if you're okay.
내가 괜찮냐고 물어봐?
They wanna know if I'm okay?
Okay, let's see.
내가 괜찮은지 궁금하다고?
보험분담금인지 뭔지로
월급이 몽땅 다 나갔고
Well, let's see.
The FlCA guys took all my money.
친구들은 결혼이나 임신,
승진했는데 난 커피나 타고 있어
Everyone is getting married
or pregnant or promoted.
And I'm getting coffee.
And it's not even for me!
그것도 남이 마실 커피를!
그래도 내가 괜찮은 것 같으면
괜찮다고 말해줘, 알았어?
If that sounds like I'm okay,
then tell them I'm okay. Okay?
레이첼이 건물 밖으로
나갔는데요
Rachel has left the building.
Can you call back?
나중에 거실래요?
좋아, 트위스터나 하자
All right! Come on!
Let's play Twister!
- 미안합니다
- 미안해요
-Sorry.
-Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
미안합니다
왜, 캐롤이랑 보냈던 그날 밤도
얼음이 얼었어?
There was ice that night with Carol?
Plastic seats?
플라스틱 의자였어?
피츠버그팬 4천명이 있었어?
Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans?
아니, 우리 자리가 떨어졌단
얘길 하려고 한 거야
No, I was just saying
we're not sitting together.
말이 나왔으니 말인데
그날 밤 얼음이 얼긴 했어
But now that you mention it,
there was ice that night.
첫 서리였지
It was the first frost.
그만하고 앉기나 해
Sit. Just sit down. Sit.
자신감을 가져
넌 독립적으로 잘하고 있어
You're doing
this amazing independent thing.
그게 뭐가 대단하다는 거야?
Monica, what is so amazing?
난 모든 걸 포기했는데
뭘 위해서지?
I gave up, like, everything.
And for what?
넌 잭이랑 같아
-You are just like Jack.
-Jack from downstairs?
아래층 사는 잭?
아니, 잭과 콩나무의 잭
No, Jack and the Beanstalk.
그 잭?
Ah, the other Jack.
그래, 잭도 뭔가를 포기했어
대신 마법의 콩을 얻었지
Right. He gave up something
but then he got those magic beans.
어느 날 잠에서 깨어보니까
콩이 엄청나게 자라서
And then he woke up
and there was this big plant...
창 밖으로 뻗어나갔지
무한한 가능성이 생긴 거야
...outside of his window,
full of possibilities.
잭은 이 마을에 살고
넌 저 마을에 사는 거야
He lived in a village,
and you live in the Village.
피비, 잭은 소를 포기했고
난 치열교정사를 포기했어
Okay. But, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow.
I gave up an orthodontist.
그이를 사랑하지 않았다는 걸
알면서도...
-Okay, I know I didn't love him....
-Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.
잭은 소를 사랑했어
그래도 그땐 계획이 있었어
분명한 계획이 있었지
But, see, it was a plan. It was clear.
모든 게 분명했는데
지금은 모든 게 전부...
Everything was figured out.
Now it's like....
- 뒤죽박죽이야?
- 그래
-Floopy?
-Yeah.
너만 그런 거 아냐, 우린 어디로
갈지 모르는 기로에 서있어
We don't know where we' re going.
그러다 어느 시점에 이르면
모든 게 분명해질 때가 올 거야
It's all gonna come together
and it's just gonna be un-floopy.
그래, 말은 쉽지
Yeah, like that's a word.
근데 말야, 모니카
그 때가 오지 않으면?
Okay. But Monica, what if
it doesn't come together?
피비?
Pheebs?
그거야...
나한테 그런 거 물어보지마
Well, because you just
I don't like this question.
우리한테 마법의 콩이
없다면 어떨까?
See, you guys?
What if we don't get magic beans?
우리가 가진 건 그냥
평범한... 콩이면?
I mean, what if all
we've got are beans?
막아라, 막아, 그래!
Get him! Get him! Get him!
Yes! You're not laughing now,
are you, pal?
그렇지
아주 잘하고 있어
이빨 없는 선수들이 치고
받고 싸우는 거 보니까 좋지?
All you needed were guys
hitting each other with sticks.
패스해, 패스
거기 비었잖아
Pass it! Pass it!
-He's open! He's open!
-Shoot it! Shoot it!
슛, 슛, 슛!
저기 봐
우리 TV에 나왔어
Hey, look, we're on that TV thing.
여기요, 여기!
응급실
실례합니다
Excuse me?
캔디바에 100% 만족하지 못하면
전화하라고 써있는데요
It says to call if you're not
satisfied with this candy bar.
전 100% 만족 못해요
Well, I'm not completely satisfied.
회사에서 제품의 맛에
책임을 져야죠
Well, the label
promises nutty goodness.
지금 응급 상황인데요
It's an emergency. But you know that,
or we'd be in the predicament room.
당장 조치를 취하지 않으면
우리도 어떻게 나올지 몰라요
잠깐만요
이거 작성하고 앉아서 기다려요
Hold on. Fill these out.
Sit over there!
이봐요
문제 일으키고 싶진 않지만
I don't want to make any trouble
but I'm in a lot of pain.
나 지금 많이 아파요
얼굴이 푹 들어갔다구요
-My face is dented.
-Well, you'll have to wait your turn.
차례를 기다려요
얼마나요?
-How long do you think it will be?
-Any minute now.
곧 될걸요
이봐요, 내 말을...
Hey, this
정말 미안해, 나 때문에
너희까지 우울해졌구나
I' m so sorry, you guys.
I didn't mean to bring you down.
아니, 네 말이 맞아
No, you were right.
I don't have a plan.
난 계획이 없어
피자 왔습니다
-Pizza guy.
-Food!
- 살았다
- 피비?
-Phoebe?
-What?
왜?
넌 계획 있니?
-Do you have a plan?
-I don't even have a " pla. "
'계'도 없어
버섯, 그린 페퍼,
양파 시키셨죠?
One mushroom, green pepper and onion?
우리 게 아니잖아, 우리 건 치즈
듬뿍 넣은 무지방 크러스트예요
No, no, no.
That's not what we ordered!
We ordered a fat-free crust
with extra cheese!
- G. 스테파노폴로스 씨 아녜요?
- 아녜요
Wait. You' re not G. Stephanopoulos?
Man, my dad's gonna kill me!
아빠한테 죽었다
잠깐만요
G. 스테파노폴로스라고 했나요?
Wait! Did you say G. Stephanopoulos?
네, 길 건너 사는 분인데
손님 걸 드렸나 봐요
Yeah, this one goes across the street.
I gave him yours. Bonehead! Bonehead!
멍청이, 멍청이!
자꾸 그러면
진짜 바보 돼요
When you do that,
you're only hitting yourself.
키 작고 지적으로 생긴
미남 말인가요?
Was this a small Mediterranean guy
with curiously intelligent good looks?
비슷하네요
-That sounds right.
-Was he wearing a stunning blue suit?
파란 양복을 입고 있던가요?
비싼 넥타이도?
-And a power tie?
-No, pretty much just a towel.
아뇨, 타월만 걸쳤던데요
맙소사, 세상에...
-Oh, God!
-You guys want me to take this back?
그냥 가져갈까요?
미쳤어요? 조지 스테파노폴로스
피자를 먹게 됐는데
What, are you nuts? We've got
George Stephanopoulos' pizza!
피비, 조지 스테파노폴로스가
누구야?
Pheebs, who's George Snuffleupagus?
친구 녀석?!
That's Big Bird's friend.
피자다!
-I see pizza!
-I want to see. Let me see.
나도 볼래, 나도 볼래
지금 누굴 보는 건데?
Hello! Who are we spying on?
백악관 고문
클린턴의 선거 유세 참모
White House adviser,
Clinton's campaign guy.
근사한 머리, 섹시한 미소,
귀여운 엉덩이, 몰라?
The one with the great hair,
sexy smile, cute butt.
그 귀여운 사람?
나도 그 사람 좋더라
Oh, him! The little guy.
Oh, I love him!
잠깐, 여자가 있어
-Wait. Wait, I see a woman.
-T ell me it's his mother.
그 사람 엄마겠지?
- 엄마는 아니다
- 안돼!
-Definitely not his mother.
-Oh, no!
거실을 걷고 있어
Wait, she's walking across the floor.
She's walking, she's walking....
계속 걸어간다
피자를 먹으려고 해
She's going for the pizza
That's not for you, bitch!
그 피자 네 거 아냐,
얌체야!
이봐요
제 친구보다 훨씬 덜 아파
보이는 사람도 왔다 가잖아요
We've been here for over an hour,
and people less sick have gone in.
발가락 찧은 사람도 벌써
진료 끝나고 갔다구요
That guy with the toe thing,
who's he sleeping with?
이러지 마, 도라
화내지 말자구
Oh, come on, Dora. Don't be mad.
우리 둘 다 진심이 아니었어
I know we both said some things...
그렇다고 우리가 사랑하지
않는 건 아냐
...we didn't mean but that doesn't
mean we still don't love each other.
애인한테 완전히 버림받았어
You know, I feel like I've lost her.
- 나 좀 밀어줘
- 싫어
-Come on, push me.
-No.
어서, 좀 밀어줘
- 그러다 다치려고
- 좀 밀어달라니까
-Push me.
-We' re gonna get in trouble.
Don't be a baby. Push me. Push me.
알았어, 밀어준다
밀어주면 되잖아
All right. I' m gonna push you, okay?
How about I push you like this?
평생 휠체어나 타고 살아라
친구야
Now you're gonna be in a wheelchair
the rest of your life, pally-wally....
정말 죄송해요
사인이라도 해드려요?
I am so very sorry. Can I sign you?
- 아직도 불 꺼졌어?
- 응
-Lights still out?
-Yeah.
둘이 낮잠 자나봐
Well, maybe they' re napping.
무슨 소리야
섹스하고 있는 거야
-Please. They' re having sex.
-Shut up!
그런 소리 마!
조지는 어떤 남자일까?
So, what do you think George is like?
수줍은 사람일 거야
-I think he's shy.
-Yeah.
그럴까?
그런데 사랑하는 여자가
본성을 끌어내는 거지
Yeah. I think you have
to draw him out.
그래서 짐승이 되는 거야
And then when you do,
he's a preppy animal.
우리 친구들은 어때?
-What do you think of the guys?
-Our guys?
- 우리 친구들?
- 그래
글쎄, 그런 얘긴 좀
뭐하지 않나?
-Yeah, our guys.
-I feel funny talking about that.
- 그러지 말고
- 좋아
-Oh, come on.
-Okay. Well....
조이가 수퍼마켓 앞에서
애들 타는 놀이기구를 보더니
I think Joey's like
a little kiddie ride.
동전을 넣고
구경하는 거 있지?
You just have to put the quarter in
and it just goes.
너희는 안 믿어지겠지만
He might surprise you. One time,
he helped me put on my coat...
언젠가 나한테 코트를
입혀주는데 정말 다정했어
...and he was really tender.
빨리 나와라, 나와
좋았어!
Come on, baby, come on. Let's go.
Yes!
챈들러는 잘 모르겠어
Chandler's one of those repressed guys
who you'd have to seduce.
뭐라고 딱 꼬집어서 말하기
힘든 타입이야
난 좀 알 것 같아
I think it's an act. Chandler is
more sophisticated than he seems.
셋 중에 제일 복잡한 인간이지
누가 제일 섹시하게?
-You know who's kind of sexy?
-Don't.
- 말하지 마
- 로스
안돼, 로스는 우리 오빠라구
-Ross.
-No, guys. Please, he is my brother.
무슨 뜻인지 알 것 같아
로스는 정말 부드러운 친구지
I know exactly what you mean.
He can be really smooth.
침대에선 어떨까?
Can't you just picture him in bed?
상상도 하기 싫다
I really don't want to.
농담이야
Come on, laugh. Laugh.
열린 창문 사이로
I remember the moonlight coming in the
window, and her face had the most...
달빛이 들어왔고 캐롤의
얼굴이 아름답게 빛났지
...incredible glow.
그래, 달, 빛, 마법 같은
감정, 아까 한 얘기야
The moon, the glow,
the magical feeling. You did this.
누가 여기 진통제 좀
갖다줘요!
Could I get some painkillers
over here, please?
그래, 제발 그만 좀 해
오늘이 뭐 대단하다고 그래?
He's right. Enough.
What's the big deal about today?
그 여자랑 처음으로 잤다고 해
그래서 어쨌단 거야?
So you slept with her
for the first time.
그 뒤로 7년 동안
계속 같이 잔 거잖아
You slept with her
for seven years after that.
그렇게 간단한 게 아냐
It's a little more complicated
그래서, 그 다음은 뭐야?
그 여자가 널 버렸잖아
What is it, that she left you
for another woman that likes women?
다른 여자를 좋아해서
그 여자 때문에 널 버린 거 아냐?
더 크게 말해
그래서 12층에 있는 의식불명
환자한테 들리겠어?
Louder. There's a man on the 1 2th
floor in a coma who didn't hear you.
그럼 뭐야?
Then, what?
캐롤이랑 했던 게 내...
My first time with Carol was...
첫...
...was my....
뭐?
What?
내 첫... 경험이라구
It was my first time.
캐롤하고?
With Carol?
Oh.
평생 한 여자랑만 한 거야?
So, in your whole life,
you've only been with one?
하키 괜히 보러 갔구만
Oh, boy. Hockey was a big mistake.
그거 말고도 할 일이
많았을 텐데
There's a bunch of stuff
we could've done tonight.
좋아, 나도 있어
Okay, I got one.
내가 만들어줬던 야채 파이,
너희가 맛있게 먹었잖아
Do you remember
that vegetarian pate...
...that I made that you loved so much?
과연 거위가 야채일까?
Well, unless goose is a vegetable!
그래, 좋아
Now I don't feel so bad
about sleeping with Jason Hurley.
제이슨 헐리랑 잔 거
너한테 하나도 안 미안해
제이슨이랑 잤어?
-What? You slept with Jason?
-You had already broken up.
너랑 헤어졌잖아
- 얼마나 사귀었어?
- 몇 시간 안 돼
-How long?
-Just a couple hours.
너무한다
-Oh, that's nice!
-Okay, okay, okay, I got one!
잠깐, 나도 있어
그렇다치고...
네 라커에 넣어둔 연애 편지
내가 쓴 거였어
Anyway, the valentine T om left in
your locker was really from me!
뭐?
Excuse me?
톰이 너한테 정말
연애편지를 보냈겠어?
Hello! Like he was really
gonna send you one.
덩치가 이따만한데
She was a big girl!
그래?
누구처럼 중학교 때
바지에 오줌싸진 않지
Really? Well, at least big girls don't
pee in their pants in seventh grade!
난 웃자고 한 얘긴데
넌 너무 심하잖아
I was laughing. You made me laugh!
저기 나온다, 저기!
Oh, my God! There he is! There he is!
- 어디?
- 밤새 우리가 쳐다보던 곳
-Where?
-Where we've been looking all night.
너무 귀엽다
-He's so cute.
-George, baby, drop the towel.
조지, 타월 좀 벗어봐요
타월 좀 벗어봐요
-Come on, drop the towel.
-Drop it. Will you please drop it?
Wow!
한 여자하고만 섹스했다는 게
믿어져?
Man, can you believe
he's only had sex with one woman?
대단하지 않냐?
I think it's great.
You know, it's sweet.
달콤하고 낭만적이고...
It's romantic.
정말?
농담하냐?
웃기는 자식이야, 알아봤다
Really?
You kidding? The guy's a freak.
I judge him.
- 이봐
- 어서와, 친구
-Hey, man!
-Hey, buddy!
Oh, that's attractive.
볼만하네요
'양들의 침묵'에서
연기 좋았어요
I thought you were great
in Silence of the Lambs.
솔직히 너도 인정해
오늘 우리 재밌었잖아
Admit it, all things considered,
you had fun tonight.
뭐가 재밌어?
특히 난, 뭐가 재밌는데?
Fun? Where was the fun?
T ell me which part was fun.
내 퍽 어딨어?
Where's my puck?
- 저 꼬마가 가져갔어
- 꼬마?
-The kid has it.
-The kid
미안하지만 그건 내 퍽이야
Excuse me, that's my puck.
내가 주웠어요, 주운 사람이
임자고 잃어버린 사람이 바보죠
I found it.
Finders keepers, losers weepers.
당하고만 있을 거야?
You gotta do it, man.
그래? 난 지우개고 넌 풀이다
그러니까...
I' m rubber, you' re glue.
Whatever you
I can't do it.
못하겠다
- 내 퍽 돌려줘
- 싫어요
-Listen, give me back my puck.
-No.
- 어서 줘
- 싫어요
-Yes, how about?
-No.
이리 와, 내 퍽 내놔
내 퍽 내놔
-Give me my puck.
-No.
- 싫어요
- 응급실에서 소란피우면 안돼요
No roughhousing in my ER!
내 퍽 내놔
Give me my puck!
퍽 하고 넘어졌네
Now that was fun.
모니카,
오른발을 빨간색에
Okay, Monica. Right foot, red.
차라리 모노폴리나 할걸...
We could've played Monopoly, but no!
고맙습니다
Thanks.
피비, 오른손을 파란색에
Okay, Pheebs. Right hand, blue.
로스, 신경 좀 써줘라
엄청나다
Ross, switch with me
and Phoebe could be number two.
뭐?
아니, 트위스터가 운동 좀
되겠다구
Nothing. It's a Twister thing.
The rules are on the back of the box.
여보세요?
Hello?
레이첼, 카드 회사야
It's the Visa card people.
대신 좀 받아줄래?
-Okay. Will you take my place?
-All right. This is Rachel.
그래
제가 레이첼인데요
아니
No!
여보세요?
알아요, 요즘 많이 안 썼죠
Hello? Oh, yeah. No, I know.
I haven't been using it much.
고맙지만 전 괜찮아요
정말요
Oh, well, thanks.
But l' m okay, really.
-To the green.
-Oh, no.
난 마법의 콩이 있거든요
I've got magic beans.
아뇨, 신경쓰지 말아요
No, no, never mind.
왼쪽으로...
T o the left! T o the left!
괜찮아
I' m fine.